Habibullah Saleem

Address: 16 Napier Avenue, Lurnea

Email: Habibullah.Saleem@student.uts.edu.au

Phone: 0406510133

Portfolio: www.hsaleem.dev

Career Objective

I am a university student graduate who recently completed a Bachelor of Science in Games Development paired with a sub major in Data Analytics. During my degree, I have maintained a distinction average, and gained a multitude of transferable and technical skills including web design & user interaction theory. I have used python, C# and C++ to program data structures, skeleton systems, and games development. Through the UX segments of my degree I am also competent in react and firebase. Thanks to my sub major I'm also experienced with Machine Learning, as I've built and integrated a CNN into web hosting through my degree.

I am hoping to gain experience in a unique workplace environment as well as develop my skills further in all possible departments.

Education 03/2020 – 11/2022

University of Technology Sydney (UTS)- Bachelor of Science (Games Development)

Career History

Rides Operator, Luna Park

Nov 2021 - Current

- Operated Rides machinery
- Liaised with customers during operation

Tutor, U@Uni (UTS Program)

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021, Sept 2022 - Current

- Taught Unity and C# in a series of workshops, and python in a 2 day workshop
- Designed curriculum and teaching materials

Team Member, KFC

Apr 2021 - Nov 2021

- Liaised with customers and management to provide consistent customer service
- Operated kitchen machinery to fulfil orders

Retail Assistant, Base Warehouse

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

- Managed inventory for the Gregory Hills chain of Base Warehouse
- · Liaised with customers and suppliers on a daily basis

Labour Force, Multiple Instances

Dec 2019 - Jan 2020

- Stocked warehouse inventory
- Organised internal inventory

Software Analyst, CBIG

Jun 2017 - Aug 2017

- Analysed data fragments and sorted them into structures
- Produced code snippets through Agile methodology

Volunteer History

Gender equity ambassador, Women in Engineering and IT (UTS)

Apr 2021 - Apr 2022

 Facilitate faculty workshops and outreach programs for face-to-face and online for primary school and high school students

Events Director, UTS Playmakers Society

Dec 2020 - Current

- Organised external and internal events for student and community engagement
- Hosted a variety of Workshops and Hackathons, whilst collaborating with a host of groups.

Referees Available upon request